F
ound
er's
Festiv
al
Bu
dget
Do
cumen
ts
Having been selected for the important role of Founder's Festival committee president,
〈創設祭実行委員長という
大役に抜てきされた少女は〉
〈忙しい日々を送っていた〉
the girl's days became very busy.
（詞）各部の予算申請書は
去年の金額と比較して
You should check the budget proposals of each club
by comparing them with the amounts allocated last year.
チェックするといいわね
Y-Yes.
（紗江）は　はい
あと　使用備品申込書の方は
もう集まってるのかしら？
Also, have you collected all the equipment request forms yet?
あッ　はい　ここに…
Yes, here...
Are most of the clubs doing what they did last year?
出し物は　ほとんどの部が
去年と同じなの？
えッ　ええッ　だったと思います
Y-Yes, I believe so.
ふ～ん　備品の確認も
しておいた方がいいわ
You should confirm we have the equipment we need.
中多さん？
昼休みに何かあったの？
Nakata-san?
Do you have something else to do this lunch break?
い　いえ　べ　別にないです
N-No, I-I don't.
すいません
色々　教えてもらって…
S-Sorry you have to help me out so much...
〈一方　少年はというと…〉
As for the boy...
〈寂しい毎日を
送っていたのである〉
His days were lonely.
〈昔のように　また　少女から〉
He had been hopeful that he'd hear the girl call him "instructor" like she used to...
〈「教官」と呼ばれることを
期待していたのだが…〉
（純一）はあ…
〈実際のところ　少年の出る幕など
なかったのである〉
But in fact, there was nothing the boy could do to help.
出逢った瞬間
Deatta shunkan
From the moment we met
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
感じてた運命を 確信に変えたくて
Kanjiteta unmei wo kakushin ni kaetakute
I wanted to change this destiny I felt into conviction
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
plus
SS
Final8 presents
Amagami
＋
Final8 presents
Amagami
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
SS
plus
＋
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
SS
＋
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
Final8 presents
plus
Amagami
今日も 君の傍に居るのかな
Kyou mo kimi no soba ni iru no ka na
I wonder if I can stay by your side again today
君の全てに
Kimi no subete ni
Everything about you
Check My Soul
ハートが動き出した
Haato ga ugokidashita
My heart begins to wake
今君と一緒に駆け出そう
Ima kimi to issho ni kakedasou
Let's break into a run together right now
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
夢のような空間の中でも
Yume no you na toki no naka de mo
Even in dreamlike moments
真実だけを見つめていたい
Shinjitsu dake wo mitsumete itai
I only want to gaze at the truth
瞳の奥の
Hitomi no oku no
Inside your eyes
Check My Soul
心の声聞いて
Kokoro no koe kiite
Listen to the voice in my heart
ゆこう この胸が高鳴る場所へ
Yukou kono mune ga takanaru basho e
Let's go to a place that will make my heart race
はあ…
There aren't any big changes with the
refreshment stalls compared to last year,
模擬店の内容を　去年と大きく
変更している部はなかったので
so we can just check it with the proposals from last year.
去年の申請書と　照らし合わせて
チェックしてみようと思ってます
そうすれば…
That way...
I made a wish.
《私　お願いしましたから》
I wished that I could be with you forever.
《ずっと先輩と一緒に
いられますようにって…》
〈少女の自分への変わらない
思いを分かっていても…〉
Even though he knew the girl's
feelings towards him hadn't changed...
〈やはり　少年の心には
すきま風が吹いていたのである〉
...the boy still felt a cold wind blow through the cracks in his heart.
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
Wish
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
Wish
Nakata Sae
2nd Half
Wish
ただいま
（美也）お帰り　早かったね
I'm home.
You're back early.
Yeah.
う～ん
あッ　そっかあ
Oh, right.
紗江ちゃんが実行委員の
お仕事で忙しいから
You have nothing to do because
Sae-chan's busy with committee work.
にぃに　ヒマなんだね
That's not the reason.
別に　そういうわけじゃ…
Sae-chan's working so hard.
紗江ちゃん　すっごい
頑張ってるもんねえ
にぃにも　何かしたら？
Why don't you do something for her?
美也に言われたくないよ
I don't wanna hear that from you.
〈とはいうものの　妹の鋭い言葉は〉
Even so, his sister's sharp words reverberated loudly in his heart.
〈少年の心に　ズシリと響いた〉
〈ますます　少女と自分の差が〉
More and more, he felt aware of the
difference between himself and the girl.
〈ついていくような
気がしていたのだ〉
"I won't be able to do anything at this rate."
〈このままだと　僕は何もできない〉
〈グズで　のろまで　無力で
ちょっとエッチな　ただのヒマ人〉
"I'm indecisive, dimwitted, hopeless, a
little perverted and I have nothing to do"...
そこまで言わなくても
いいんじゃないかな！？
Do you really have to go that far?
〈うッ　うん〉
As a bear about to go into hibernation,
I have to make sure I eat my fill before then.
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]冬眠前のクマさんは
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]おなかを　いっぱいに
しておかないとダメなんです
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]ごめんなさい　だから
あなたを食べちゃいます
Sorry, but I'll have to eat you up.
Rawr!
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]ガオ～ッ！
そうだ　これがあった！
That's right! I have this!
〈少年の　この顔から察するに〉
Judging from the boy's face, I get the
feeling he's thinking of something pointless...
〈何やら　ろくでもないことを
考えている気がするのだが…〉
いってきま～す
I'm heading off!
えッ　にぃに
もう出かけるの？
Nii-nii, you're going already?
今日は　やけに早いね
You're unusually early today.
Founder's Festival
Committee Headquarters
えッ　ドキュメンタリーですか？
Huh? A documentary?
実行委員長の
紗江ちゃんの仕事ぶりに
I'll follow you closely as you go about your work
as committee president and record it all on camera!
僕が密着して　その様子を
カメラに収めるんだよ
〈やはり予感は的中である〉
My hunch was indeed correct.
きっと　今後の参考にもなるし
It'll make a good reference and I also want to try doing non-fiction for the first time.
それに僕としても　ノンフィクションに
初挑戦してみたいと思ってるんだ
すごく面白そうですね　先輩
私も　やってみたいです
That sounds really interesting!
Senpai, I'd like to give it a try too.
Hey girl, are you sure about that?
〈少女よ　それでいいのか？〉
Well then, let's start today...
じゃあ　早速　今日から
いや　今からいいかな？
No, would right now be okay?
はい　もちろんです　監督！
Yes, of course, director!
さ　紗江ちゃん
S-Sae-chan.
もう一度　そう呼んでくれないかな
Could you call me that again?
はい…　監督
Yes, director!
よしッ！　じゃあ　まず
実行委員長になって
All right!
Let's start with your thoughts on
becoming the committee president.
紗江ちゃんが　今
どんな気持ちでいるのか
語ってみようか
は　はい
O-Okay.
よ～い　アクション！
Ready... action!
Um...
えっと…　生まれて初めて
It's the first time in my life I've
been given such a big... um... big job...
こんな大きな…　えっと…
大きな　お仕事を任されまして
あの…　うまくできるか
不安なんですけど…
Um... I don't know if it'll all go well, but I'll try my very best...
でも　精一杯頑張ろうと…
（戸が開く）
Good morning, school council president.
おはようございます　生徒会長
Oh, Ayatsuji-san. Morning.
あッ　絢辻さん　おはよう
おはよう　それは？
Good morning. What's that?
あの…　創設祭実行委員のお仕事を
カメラで撮るんです
Um... we're recording what a Founder's
Festival committee member does on camera.
えッ？
記録として残そうかなって
I figured we'd create a record of it...
思って…
そう　それはいいわね
I see.
That sounds good.
ただし　私はあまり映さないでね
Though...
Don't film me too much, okay?
えッ？　あれッ
この部屋　何か寒い…
Huh? It's kinda chilly in this room for some reason...
どう？　うまくいってる？
So, are things going well?
はい　この前　教えて
もらったことから始めてます
Yes, I started with what you told me before.
Okay.
そう　ところで
飲食関連の模擬店用の
By the way, make sure you don't forget about the ingredients order list for the food refreshment stalls.
食材発注リストも
忘れないようにね
あッ　すみません
そっちは　まだ…
Sorry, I haven't gotten around to that yet...
なるべく早めにしておいた方が
いいと思うわ
You should do that ahead of time, since you might not get everything you need if you do it last-minute.
ギリギリになってからだと
揃わなくなるかもしれないから
Y-Yes, I understand.
は　はい　分かりました　すみません
Sorry.
まだ時間あるから　心配ないわ
You still have time, so don't worry.
他の実行委員と手分けして
高橋先生にも相談するといいわよ
Get the other committee members to
help and discuss it with Takahashi-sensei.
は　はい　食材の件は
今日中に　私が確認しておきます
O-Okay.
I'll confirm the food ingredients later today.
（詞が教室を出ていく）
〈それは今まで　少年が
見たことのない　少女の顔だった〉
The boy had never seen the girl's face like that before.
（チャイムが鳴る）
（麻耶）はい　じゃあ
今日はここまで
Okay, let's stop here for today.
Boss, we haven't had lunch together in a while, so how about it?
（梅原）大将！　久々に
飯　一緒にどうだ？
一人じゃ寂しいだろ？
悪い　用があるんだ
It's lonely eating by yourself.
Sorry, I have something to do.
つれないなあ　大将
That's cold, boss.
結局　今の俺には
これしかないってことか…
I guess this is all I have now, then...
おッ　それ！？
≪（美也）お兄ちゃん！
Whoa, is that...?!
Onii-chan!
Sae-chan's in trouble!
紗江ちゃんが大変だよ！
えッ！？
What?!
紗江ちゃん！　あッ…
Sae-chan!
Sae-chan...
紗江ちゃん…
あッ　ダメ…
No...
S-Sae-chan?
さ　紗江ちゃん…
Please... no...
ダメ…　です…
えッ！？
橘先輩…　ラメ～ッ！
Tachibana-senpai...
No!
あッ　にぃに！
美也！
Nii-nii!
Miya!
What are you doing?!
何してんの！
違うんだ　美也
You got it wrong, Miya!
何が違うの？
何もしてない…
What did I get wrong?
I didn't do anything...
But Sae-chan was screaming "No"!
だって今　紗江ちゃん
「ラメ～ッ！」って
紗江ちゃんが寝言で…
う　う～ん…
Sae-chan's just talking in her sleep...
紗江ちゃん！　何されたの？
Sae-chan! What did he do to you?
えッ　美也ちゃん？
私　寝ちゃって…
Miya-chan...
I fell asleep...
Ah, Senpai?
あッ　先輩…
紗江ちゃん　大丈夫？
Sae-chan, are you okay?
具合が悪いんじゃないのか？
Are you not feeling very well?
えッ　いいえ…
No...
きのうの夜
遅くまで起きていたので
I was up late last night, so I thought I'd take a nap this lunch break...
お昼休みに
ちょっと仮眠しようと思って…
そうだったのか　まったく
美也は大げさなんだよ！
I see.
Seriously, Miya makes such a big deal out of things.
エヘヘヘッ…
Sorry I worried you, but I'm fine now that I've had some sleep.
心配かけてすみません
でも　少し寝られたので
もう大丈夫です
That's good.
よかった
ところで
By the way, what were you dreaming about?
紗江ちゃん　どんな夢見てたの？
〈少女が　一体
どんな夢を見ていたのか〉
The boy really wanted to know what the girl had been dreaming about.
〈とても気になる少年であった〉
School Staff Room
あの…　水泳部のおでんとか
Um...
About the ingredients for the Swim Club's oden, the Basketball Club's yakisoba and the Tea Club's sweet sake...
バスケット部の焼きそばとか
茶道部の甘酒の材料とかは
えっと…
Um...
同じ　お店で一括して買った方が
安く済むんじゃないかと
I was thinking it'd be cheaper to
buy them all from the same store.
Indeed, that sounds like a good idea.
そうね　それは
いい考えじゃないかしら
Okay, I'll talk to the heads of each club.
はい　じゃあ　各部の
部長さんに　お話してみます
そういえば　茶道部って
甘酒の材料
By the way, did the Tea Club request for the
same amount of sweet sake as they did last year?
去年と同じ量を
申請してるのかしら？
はい　そうだったと思います
Yes, I believe so.
足りないんじゃないかしら？
えッ？
That wouldn't be enough...
いいわ　それは私が直接
茶道部に　お願い…
It's fine, I'll beg the Tea Club directly...
いえ　確認しておくから
I mean, I'll confirm it with them.
Okay, thank you.
はい　お願いします
こんな感じでいいかしら？
Was that okay?
Yes, it's perfect, Sensei!
はい　バッチリです　先生
そう　ならいいけど
Okay, that's good.
Fried Dough Cake
Grounds
Special
For rent
Oden
Yakisoba
Udon
Chocolate Banana
Gym
Fried Dough Cake
〈一生懸命に頑張っている
少女の姿を　カメラに収めることで〉
In capturing how hard the girl was working on
camera, he felt that he was doing his part as well.
〈何か　自分も一緒に
頑張っている気がすると〉
Those were his thoughts at the time.
〈その時は　思っていたのだ〉
Huh? Um...
えッ　えっと…
予算の追加ですか？
An increase in the budget?
This was ten days before the Founder's Festival.
〈それは　創設祭を１０日後に控えた
ある日のことだった〉
Yes.
（演劇部部長）ええ　思いの外
舞台装置に　お金がかかって
The stage equipment cost more than expected, so the allocated budget isn't enough at all.
全然　予算が足らないの
このままだと衣装が買えなくて…
At this rate, we won't be able to buy costumes...
But we've already increased your budget compared to last year.
でも…　今年はもともと
去年より上乗せした
予算だったんですよね？
それでも足りないんですか？
Is it still not enough?
（演劇部部長）そうなんだけど…
You're right, but...
委員長　そこを何とか
お願いします！
Prez, please do something!
Founder's Festival Budget Request Form
そうなの
演劇部が予算の追加をね…
Founder's Festival Budget Request Form
Group Name
Drama Club
Founder's Festival Budget Request Form
Group Name
Drama Club
Founder's Festival Budget Request Form
Group Name
Drama Club
I see.
So the drama club's requesting a budget increase.
はい…
それと
Yes...
That and the equipment the Swim Club and the
Tea Club had been using until last year is getting old,
去年まで　水泳部と茶道部が
使っていた備品が
古くなっていて　新しいのを
買ってほしいと…
so they'd like new equipment to be bought...
これ　今になって分かったの？
It took you this long to find out?
すみません　備品の
チェックが遅れてしまって…
Sorry, the equipment checking ran late...
Well, no point in worrying about that.
じゃあ　仕方ないわね
演劇部の件はともかく
The drama club's request aside, we'll figure something out about the new equipment.
備品は何とかしましょう
よろしくお願いします
Thank you.
Sae-chan.
紗江ちゃん
先輩…
Senpai...
What's wrong?
どうかしたの？
私　失敗ばかりで…
I keep making mistakes.
やっぱり　こんな大事な仕事
I'm thinking this big job really is too much for me to handle.
私には無理だったんじゃ
ないかなって…　思います
どうして
引き受けちゃったのかな…
I'm wondering why I decided to do it.
て　思います
紗江ちゃん　大丈夫？
Sae-chan, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
はい　大丈夫です
あの…
（実行委員１）委員長！→
Um-
Prez!
Can I have a minute?
ちょっといいですか？
あッ　はい　じゃあ
Okay.
See you.
心配してくれて
ありがとうございます
Thanks for worrying about me.
The boy felt useless for being unable to help the girl.
〈少年は　少女に手を貸してやる
ことができない自分を〉
〈ふがいなく思っていた〉
はあ…
That was a pretty big sigh.
随分　大きな　ため息ね
どうかしたの？
What's wrong?
絢辻さん…　そうだ！
ちょっといいかな？
Ayatsuji-san...
Oh, right! Do you have a minute?
えッ？
そうだったの
うん
I see.
Yeah.
去年の私もね
今の中多さんみたいに
Last year, just like Nakata-san, I was panicking, thinking I had to do everything myself.
ちゃんと自分で
やらなくちゃって焦ったり
私には無理かもって
悩んだりしたんだけど…
I was worried it might all be too much for me.
Even you?
絢辻さんが？
私だって悩むわよ
I worry about things too!
いや…　その…
Well, um...
でもね　頼れる時は
人に頼ればいいのよ
You just need to ask others for help when you need it, though.
何でも　自分一人で
解決しなくちゃって
Don't hold on to the belief that you have to solve everything yourself.
抱え込むことないもの
そうだね
Indeed.
Shouldn't you just tell Nakata-san that?
橘君が中多さんに　そう言って
あげればいいんじゃない？
Huh? Me?
えッ　僕が？
だって
Well, aren't you having this discussion
with me because you're worried about her?
今も中多さんのことが心配で
私に相談してるんでしょ？
I guess that's true...
まあ　そうだけど…
How nice.
いいな～　そうやって
I'm jealous that she has someone by
her side who'll always worry about her.
いつも　そばで
心配してくれる人がいて
うらやましいな～
えッ　そうかな…
Really...
〈そうやって
すぐに調子に乗るのは〉
The boy has a bad habit of being easily swayed.
〈少年の悪いクセである〉
However, the boy was thinking, "Yes, it's not enough
to just be by her side. I also have to support Sae-chan".
〈だが　少年は思っていた〉
〈「そう　ただ　そばに
いるだけではダメなんだ」〉
〈「僕が紗江ちゃんを
支えなければ」と〉
〈そのとおりだ　少年！〉
That's exactly it, boy!
絢辻さん　ありがとう
Ayatsuji-san, thank you!
（教師）ここ　重要なので
よく覚えておくように
This part's important, so make sure you remember it.
（チャイムが鳴る）
Founder's Festival
Committee Headquarters
（ノック）
Yes?
はい
Senpai...
先輩…
紗江ちゃんに
見せたいものがあるんだ
There's something I want to show you.
えッ？
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]もう少しで完成ですね
It's almost done.
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]（実行委員１）あと一踏ん張り
Just a little more to go!
Um... how about using this color here?
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]えっと　ここは
この色で　どうでしょうか？
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]（実行委員２）いい感じ
Looks good!
Prez, your aesthetic sense is really great!
[ﾃﾚﾋﾞ]（実行委員３）
委員長　センス抜群だね
Senpai, you even managed to capture these scenes too?
先輩　こんなところまで
撮ってたんですか？
フッフッフ…　僕はずっと
紗江ちゃんのそばにいて
I've been collecting footage by
following you closely the whole time.
密着取材しているからね
あのさ　紗江ちゃん…
You know, Sae-chan...
悩んだり　壁にぶつかったりしたら
言ってくれないかな？
Whenever you're worried about something or hit a wall, could you tell me?
えッ？
Well, maybe I can't really be of help, but...
いや　僕じゃ　頼りに
ならないかもしれないけど…
そばにいるだけじゃなくて
I want to do more than just be by
your side. I want to be your strength.
僕　紗江ちゃんの力になりたいんだ
先輩…
Senpai...
Yes, thank you.
はい　ありがとうございます
で　早速だけど
僕にできることあるかな？
So, is there anything I can do right now?
はい…　じゃあ　ひとつ
お願いしてもいいですか？
Right...
Okay, could you do something for me?
うん　何？
Yeah. What?
U-Um...
あの…　密着取材なんですけど
Could you continue to follow me closely and film me?
このまま
続けてもらっていいですか？
あの…　ずっと私のこと
見ていてほしいんです
Um... I want you to look at me the whole time.
もちろんだよ　紗江ちゃん
But of course, Sae-chan.
あッ…
うん？
Um... that video...
あの…　この映像は…
うわッ！
先輩？
Senpai?
This isn't anything!
これは…　何でもない！
ちょっと向こう見てて
Look away for a sec.
Founder's Festival
Committee Headquarters
What? Really?!
≪（演劇部部長）ええッ　ホント！？
I managed to rent some old costumes from the store at the shopping district.
商店街の貸衣装屋さんで
古くなった衣装を
いただいてきました
Wow, these are amazing!
へえ～ッ　すごいよ　これ
ありがとう
Thank you!
あと　もしこれで足りなければ
私が衣装を　お作りします
If these aren't enough, I can make costumes for you.
えッ　委員長が？
Huh? You?
はい　実は私
ドレスを縫ったことがあるんです
Yes.
I've made dresses myself before.
Ooh... I'll take you up on your offer, then!
へえ～ッ　じゃあ
お願いしようかな
はい
Okay!
She had told the boy that her mother made the dress.
〈そのドレスというのは　少年には〉
〈「母親が縫った」と思わず
言ってしまった〉
〈あのウエディングドレスのことである〉
You know what wedding dress I'm talking about.
〈ついに　創設祭当日がやってきた〉
At long last, it was the day of the Founder's Festival.
Kibitou High School
Founder's Festival
〈そして　それは少女の
晴れ舞台でもあった〉
It would also be the girl's big moment.
（深呼吸する紗江）
Sae-chan, go for it.
紗江ちゃん　頑張れ
Senpai, I'll do my best.
〈先輩　頑張ります〉
ただいまより　輝日東高校創設祭を
The Kibitou High School Founder's Festival will now begin!
開催いたします！
（逢）どうぞ　熱いので
気をつけてください
Here you go!
Oden
Girls Swim Club
Egg
Konnyaku
It's hot, so please be careful.
[ｽﾋﾟｰｶ]ただいまより　ベストカップルコンテストを
開催いたします！
The Best Couple Contest will now begin!
Best Couple Contest
Waiting Room
出場者順で
ステージ袖まで行ってください
Please head to the stage wing
in the order you'll be presented.
≪（美也）紗江ちゃ～ん
Sae-chan!
うわ～ッ　美也ちゃん
やっぱり似合うね
Ooh, Miya-chan!
It really does look good on you!
Really?
ホント？　他でもない
紗江ちゃんの　お願いだからね
I'm only doing this because you asked me to, Sae-chan.
美也　張り切っちゃうよ！
I'm gonna let myself loose!
ニャ～ッ！
ねえ　私達
Hey, do we even fit with the whole point of the Best Couple Contest?
ベストカップルコンテストの
趣旨に合ってるのかな？
Toroko! We'll definitely win this year!
トロ子　今年こそ
優勝を手にするぞ！
何でもありなんだね
I guess everything goes.
じゃあ　行ってくるニャン
Well, off we go!
（美也）ヒャア
美也ちゃん　カワイイ
Miya-chan, you're so cute!
たまには私が美也ちゃんを…
I'll have to pet you once in a while!
もふもふしちゃう～！
紗江ちゃんに逆襲された～！
Sae-chan's attacking me back!
（はしゃぐ紗江と美也）
Stop, Sae-chan!
I won't hold back!
Not there!
I'll get you back for this!
（ドアが閉まる）
あッ　先輩
Senpai.
お疲れさま　紗江ちゃん
Good work, Sae-chan.
先輩　すみません
Senpai, I'm sorry.
ずっとバタバタしていて
I've been running all over the place and didn't really talk to you much...
なかなか先輩と　お話できなくて…
いや　いいんだよ
ちょっと待っててください
Nah, it's fine.
Wait just a bit.
これ　クリスマスプレゼントです
It's your Christmas present.
えッ　僕　今日は
何も用意してないんだけど…
I didn't prepare anything for you today, though...
ごめん…
いいんです
Sorry.
It's fine, don't worry.
気にしないでください　はい
Here.
ありがとう
Th-Thanks.
気に入ってもらえると
いいんですけど…
I hope you like it.
何かな？
後で　ゆっくり開けてみてください
What is it?
Please take your time opening it later.
あの　もしよかったら
Um, if you don't mind, could you tell me what you'd like?
紗江ちゃんのほしいもの
教えてくれないかな？
えッ　ほしいものですか？
うん
What I'd like?
Yeah.
う～ん…
だったら…
うん？
In that case...
最近　全然…　してないから…
We haven't... done it in a long time...
What?
何？
キ　キス…　してないから…
W-We haven't... kissed...
えッ？
（外で生徒達の歓声がする）
もう少しだけ…
Just a little more...
うん…
Yeah.
It was the best Christmas present the girl could hope for.
〈それは少女にとって〉
〈最高のクリスマスプレゼント
だったのである〉
8 Years Later
Go, Inago Mask Ultra Hyper Third!
いっけーッ！　イナゴマスク
ウルトラハイパーサードォ～！→
Don't lose, Inago Mask!
負けるなー！　イナゴマスクゥー！
あッ　動いた！
えッ？
Ah, it moved!
赤ちゃんもイナゴマスク
応援してるのかな？
Do you think the baby's cheering for Inago Mask too?
そうだな
Seems like it.
そうね
Indeed.
She was enjoying the Hero Show with the boy and her family.
〈少年と　そして家族と一緒に
ヒーローショーで盛り上がる〉
〈それこそが　少女が
あの日　神社で祈願した〉
That was the other wish the girl
had made at the shrine that day.
〈もうひとつの
お願いだったのである〉
〈ともあれ　この二人が
いつまでも　こうして〉
At any rate, let's wish from the bottom of our hearts that the two of them will remain in love forever.
〈ラブラブなままで
あることを心から願おう〉
朝を運ぶバイクの音が
Asa wo hakobu baiku no oto ga
The sound of bicycles each morning brings
僕に時間の流れ告げ
Boku ni toki no nagare tsuge
Tells me of the passage of time
もうどこへも行けない気持ち
Mou doko e mo ikenai kimochi
My feelings have nowhere else to go
君に渡す覚悟決めた
Kimi ni watasu kakugo kimeta
I've decided to tell you about them
未来に散りばめた 予定は隣に 君がいてほしい
Mirai ni chiribameta yotei wa tonari ni kimi ga ite hoshii
I want you right by my side in my plans for the future
息を吸って吐き出す
Iki wo sutte hakidasu
I take deep breaths in and out
言葉は幾度もため息に変わるけど
Kotoba wa ikudo mo tameiki ni kawaru kedo
My words keep turning into sighs
伝えたい言葉はただひとつだけ
Tsutaetai kotoba wa tada hitotsu dake
But there's just one thing I want you to know
好きだよ
Suki da yo
"I love you"
僕の告白
Boku no kokuhaku
It's my confession
Preview
次回予告
Next episode preview.
It's finally my turn, Tachibana-kun!
（はるか）いよいよ次から
私の出番なのね　橘君！
Yes, that's right, Morishima-senpai!
はい　そうですよ
森島先輩
こんなにジラされたら　色々
期待しちゃうじゃない
Geez...
Now I'll expect all sorts of things
because you made me wait so long.
い　色々って…
色々は　色々よ
B-By all sorts of things, you mean...
All sorts of things.
色々って！
女の子の口から言わせないで
Which means?!
Oh come on, you
shouldn't make a girl say it.
次回「セクシー」って
N-Next episode: "Sexy".
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
1st Half
Sexy
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
1st Half
Sexy
Next Episode
Morishima Haruka
1st Half
Wait, is this episode title really okay?
何か言い訳のきかない
サブタイトルなんですけど
Well, everyone, are you ready?
（はるか）さあ　みんな
準備はいい？